// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers

let questions = [
  {
   numb: 1,
   question: 'What is the average lifespan of sloths in the wild?',
   answer: '20-25 years',
   options: [
          '15-20 years',
          '20-25 years',
          '30-35 years',
          '40-45 years'
        ]
    },
    {
    numb:2,
    question: 'How many hours does it take for a sloth to digest a meal?',
    answer: '36-48 hours',
    options: [
          '6-8 hours',
          '12-24 hours',
          '36-48 hours', 
          '72-96 hours'
              ]
          },
          {
    numb:3,
    question: 'Which of the following is true about sloths fur?',
    answer: 'It grows in the opposite direction to other mammals',
    options: [
            'It is naturally blue in colour',
            'It grows in the opposite direction to other mammals',
            'It sheds once a year',
            'It is resistant to parasites'
              ]
                }, 
            {
    numb:4,
    question: 'What is the weight of a newborn sloth?',
    answer: '1-2 pounds',
    options: [
          '1-2 pounds',
          '3-5 pounds', 
          '6-8 pounds',
          '9-11 pounds'
        ]
    },
    {
      numb:5,
        question: 'Who is a natural predator of sloths?',
        answer: 'jaguars',
        options: [
          'jaguars',
          'elephants',
          'crocodiles',
          'gorillas'
        ]
    },
    {
      numb:6,
        question: 'Where are sloths found in the wild?',
        answer: 'Central and South America',
        options: [
          'Africa',
          'Asia',
          'Australia',
          'Central and South America'
        ]
    },
    {
      numb:7,
        question: 'How many hours a day do sloths sleep?',
        answer: '12-14 hours',
        options: [
          '8-10 hours',
          '10-12 hours',
          '12-14 hours', 
          '14-16 hours'
        ]
    },
    {
      numb:8,
        question: 'How many chambers does a sloth stomach have?',
        answer: 'two',
        options: [
          'one', 
          'two', 
          'three', 
          'four'
        ]
    },
    {
      numb:9,
        question: 'Which sense is the best for sloths?',
        answer: 'smell',
        options: [
          'sight',
          'taste',
          'touch',
          'smell'
        ]
    },
    {
      numb:10,
        question: 'What is the main diet of a sloth?',
        answer: 'leaves',
        options:
        [
          'insects',
          'meat',
          'leaves',
          'fish'
        ]
    }
  ]
